So you're Corpse?
Sir Hado, let us take Corpse out for you.
That's fine. Have at him.
Yes, sir!
Let's go!
It's like they're not even moving...
That's the difference in your stats.
I can deal with them using Ruinous Strike.
Spare us!
Wait! Get back here!
Damn it... you think you
can make a fool of me?
You're just a monster!
You won't get away with this!
How is trash like you this powerful?!
Fate!
I don't owe you an explanation.
Don't... don't get mouthy with me!
You think you'll get away with this?!
Do you realize who you're dealing with?!
I'm the second son of the Vlerick family...
The holy knight Hado Vlerick!
Then why don't you show me
the holy knight powers you're so proud of?
To Galia
Holy Sword Technique...
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Holy Sword Technique,
Strength Boost (High)
The special skill you need
to become a holy knight.
Why'd someone like him end up with it?
Greed, can you shatter a holy sword?
There is no chance some orichalcum-cut
artificial holy sword has the edge on me.
Strike as you like.
Good to know.
Idiot. You'd actually face down
my sword at this range...
You really are intellectually bankrupt trash!
Grand Cross!
Let the holy light purify you
until nothing's left!
That takes way too long to deploy.
Impossible... this is a holy sword!
Here's the rest of your precious holy sword.
Pick it up.
Don't run. I thought you were a holy knight.
This is pathetic.
What's wrong?
You really are a joke.
On your feet! I think you need
to be taught a lesson.
"Defiant dogs need strict discipline," right?
Stop...
Please... just stop...
The nerve you have to say that.
After how you treated people like insects...
And now Lady Roxy is heading into danger
because of filth like you!
Please... spare me...
What was your response when I said that?!
Bloody Ptarmigan, now!
I'll be taking some of your stats!
You didn't finish me off... Why?
Just kill me.
I have questions first.
About Roxy Hart...?
She...
I will go.
If my life can save even
a single citizen of this kingdom...
Then I will gladly head to Galia.
She would say that.
I'll... get Roxy's Galia
expedition canceled...
J-Just... spare me...
Don't... don't do something stupid...
like getting revenge for her sake!
Shut up.
This is for me.
It's my revenge!
Gluttony skill has activated.
Increasing stats.
[Stats]
Vitality:
Strength:
Magic:
Spirit:
Agility:
[Skills]
Gluttony, Identify, Telepathy
Conceal, Night Vision, Brawler,
Holy Sword Technique
One-Handed Sword Technique,
Two-Handed Sword Technique
Strength Boost (Low)
Strength Boost (Med)
Strength Boost (Large)
Vitality Boost (Low)
Vitality Boost  (Med)
Agility Boost (Med)
Health Regen
Skill Holy Sword Technique has been added.
Looks like you're a holy knight now.
The capital would never accept that.
Besides...
I wouldn't want to be one.
That's what I figured.
So, how about this? Right now,
you can access my second level.
Do it. The idea of his stats being
inside me makes me want to puke.
I bet. Here we go!
This is my second level:
a great scythe.
The curse embedded in the blade
can cut through even the ephemeral.
It can cut through anything...?
I wish it could cut short
Lady Roxy's trip to Galia.
Everyone, don't look so forlorn.
Three years will be over before you know it.
Look after things while I'm gone, Haru.
As head of the Hart family,
please serve with honor.
Lady Roxy...
Good luck to you.
Fay...
Lady Roxy...
I—
Fay...
We'll meet again, Fate.
Yes. Please, look after yourself, Lady Roxy.
I'm heading off.
Lady Roxy left a letter
of recommendation for me?
Yes. If you were employed
in a lord's manor,
you'd be out of reach for the Vlericks.
She was worried about me
until the very end...
I can't accept this.
Fate?
I'm going to make my way
as a warrior from now on.
Looks like you've made up your mind.
Yeah.
If I can't stop Lady Roxy from going
to Galia, I can at least support her.
We're gonna miss you.
Come back whenever you like.
What you've earned up to today,
along with some severance pay.
This seems like a lot...
Never forget the pride that comes
from serving the Hart family.
Good luck, Fate!
Right!
Until we meet again.
And in order for that to happen...
I need to head to Galia.
With my power... I'll protect Lady Roxy.
Things are shaping up nicely.
I have taken over the post
held by my father, Mason Hart.
Heading towards the border,
in order to fell the Divine Dragon that
has awoken, after a millennium of silence,
so that I may defend the royal capital,
Seifort, and its people.
And I will need your help.
Lady Roxy!
Miria, you're joining, too?
Of course I am! Wherever you go,
I'll be right behind you.
You volunteered too, missy?
Likewise.
Huh? "Missy"?
Sorry, sorry. The name's Mugan.
I'm Miria.
Miria, huh? It's a pleasure.
I know your type.
People excited at the chance to see the living
natural disaster that is a Divine Dragon...
Reckless oddballs looking for
a chance to test their mettle.
Can't deny that.
Most warriors relish the chance to see just
how far their strength can take them.
Great, an idiot warrior.
Miria, that's going too far.
Yay! I got scolded by Lady Roxy!
I volunteered because of Sir Mason, though.
I marched under his orders, once.
And as presumptuous as it may be,
I'd like to avenge him.
I see. Thank you.
But, wouldn't your family
oppose a trip to Galia?
My daughter, Raine, actually
asked me for some Galian relics.
Galian... relics?
I come from a long line of scholars
who do research. I'm the only warrior.
Wow, that's amazing! Apart from you, Mugan.
Just had to throw that in there, huh?
I feel like, with the two of you,
this trip may work out.
I'll be counting on you.
Right!
Raine? Do you have a moment?
You know the lich called Corpse,
the monster that everyone's
been talking about, right?
These are the goblins it's been slaying...
Look here. These aren't
normal arrow wounds, are they?
That is rather fascinating.
Here.
I think this is it. Magic arrows.
Magic arrows? And that's different
from Fireball magic?
It's an ability housed in the black sword,
one of the Weapons of Mortal Sin.
The Weapons of Mortal Sin
are made of a material
that can manipulate magic
power at a high level.
The Weapons of Mortal Sin? What are those?
Not sure...
But if they can control magic power, they'd
expand the possibility spectrum for skills.
I'd like to see that...
One of these Weapons of Mortal Sin.
Gentlemen, we're nearly at Tetra.
The hub for shipping headed
towards the royal capital.
A city of merchants, where the best
goods in the south are gathered...
Tetra.
It hasn't changed much.
What, you've been here before?
Yeah. Five years ago.
I just passed through
on the way to the capital.
I see.
Excuse me.
Is this carriage headed for Galia?
Not today, it's not. If I headed out now,
I'd get attacked by monsters in the night.
Come by again tomorrow.
Okay.
That's tough luck.
You wanna run off after Roxy,
but you're stuck here for now.
Shut up!
What was that?
Oh, just talking to myself! Sorry.
I say you grab something to eat
and gather intel for now.
I guess so.
After that comes shopping.
If this is a big trade town, there might
be a scabbard worthy of me here.
Are you going on about that, again?
Naturally!
I mean, you've got the Holy
Sword Technique skill now, Fate.
That means the scabbard
needs to live up to it.
Maybe something decorated with orichalcum...
No, wait, magic crystals would be good, too.
I've got that severance pay
from Miss Haru...
I may as well enjoy some meat today.
Are you listening?
Please, my village needs help!
If nothing is done, it could...
You think this chump change
is enough to get us to hunt monsters?
And you're begging for help?
You want our help, then you oughta
show how much it means to you!
Come on!
That's enough.
Who the hell are you?!
Who do you think you are?!
Fine! Fine, just...
Please, let us go!
Who is this guy?!
Let's get out of here!
Y-Yeah...
You saved me. Thank y—
It's been a while, Set.
Fate?
All you do is growl with your stomach,
you good-for-nothing.
Good-for-nothing!
Stop! Cut it out, Set!
Monsters! Monsters are attacking!
Dad?
You've gotten used to handling herbs, I see.
Only because you get hurt all the time, Dad.
Here.
Thanks.
Man, that's bitter...
Dad...
Why'd you have to die?
Dean had the Spear Technique skill,
so the village chief kept him around, but...
Who's gonna look after this extra mouth?
Get out of here, you worthless garbage!
Go on, good-for-nothing!
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Fate, please! I need your help!
Fate...
This is Set, the son
of the village chief who exiled me.
I realize how self-centered this is...
But... you're a warrior now,
and I need that strength!
Come on, this works out nicely, Fate.
You need to sate Gluttony anyway.
Fine.
I'll handle your monster problem.
Really?
What a relief. I wasn't sure you'd accept...
Let's go.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't still resent them.
But that village... I have
memories of my father there.
For pity's sake...
You actually brought the garbage
that we exiled back with you.
What is the meaning of this, Set?
Fate's strong! I saw him defeat
some warriors with my very own eyes!
This is pathetic! You can't even
hire some warriors properly?
I'm sorry, everyone,
I'll find us some warriors tomorrow.
But if the monsters attack first...
There's been cries from
a nearby forest since yesterday!
I don't know if we can last
until the warriors arrive!
Then we'll use him as a sacrifice
to buy us some time.
Fate! Please, just let it go.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for earlier.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
I've been wondering, where's
your wife? I haven't seen her.
Did the monsters get her?
Yeah... The village is still as poor as ever.
The village chief has absolute authority,
and I... I used to think my old man
was always right, too.
But...
Since my daughter was born,
I realized I needed to get
my act together, for her sake.
You've really changed.
All thanks to her.
Set, tell me about these monsters.
Sure.
They first showed up about a month ago...
The witnesses make it sound
like there's more than one.
They can apparently fly, too.
That sounds like bad news.
Yeah... They're nothing like the monsters
the village has had to deal with before.
That's why we decided to hire some warriors.
Without realizing the market price...
Still hungry as ever?
Hang on a sec.
They probably thought things would work out
if they could hire some warriors.
Pretty typical story with small villages.
But if these monsters can fly,
that changes everything.
You have an idea what
we're dealing with, Greed?
Yeah. They're most likely gargoyles.
As monsters go, they're on the clever side.
They start by doing probing attacks
to see how humans react...
And when the time is right,
the entire pack attacks in a swarm.
A lot like kobolds.
Who are you talking to?
Uh... just to myself, that's all.
You can have this.
Thanks.
You wanna play for a while?
Yeah!
Okay...
Come on!
Sorry, I don't have much to offer.
No. I appreciate it.
What is this...?
I'm suddenly... tired...
Fate?! What's wrong?
How could this happen?
Did he eat something weird?
I gave him some candy.
Candy?
Yeah. Grandpa gave it to me.
Dad... Damn it. Is he serious
about sacrificing Fate?
I get it. Drugged candy, huh?
Fate! You gotta wake up, Fate!
The Girl of Wrath
"The Girl of Wrath."